Guide to the Henry Ernest Sigerist Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1897-(1913-1957)-1970; Series I; 12 linear feet (30 boxes)
  - General, 1931-1946
    - Sudhoff, Karl(*), 1931-1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - Supporters of Democracy and Peace, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - T (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Temkin, Owsei(*), 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 234-235)
    - Temkin, Owsei(*), 1937-1945 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - Thieme (Georg) Verlag
      See: box 14, folder 509
    - Ulich, Robert, 1932, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 237)
      See also: box 36, folder 98-99
    - V (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Viets, Henry R., 1933 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Vonwiller, Paul, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - W (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Weed, Lewis Hill, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Weisberger, Rosamond Hollander(Mrs. Siegfried), 1934 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Weisberger, Siegfried, 1931-1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Welch, William H.(*), 1931-1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Williams, Huntington, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Winslow, Charles-Edward Amory, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Winternitz, Milton Charles, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Yale University School of Medicine, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Z (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Zeiss, Henry, 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Zilboorg, Gregory, 1931, 1942, undated (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Zilboorg, Margaret (Mrs. Gregory), 1942, 1945, undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Zilboorg, Ray (Mrs. Gregory), 1931 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - General, 1947-1957
    - A (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Aall, Lily, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Abascal, Horacio, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Abegg, Emil, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Abegg, Lily, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Abelard-Schuman, Inc., 1954, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 254)
      See also: box 22, folder 779
    - Abrams, Herbert K., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Abramsky, J. D., undated (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Abrashkin, Raymond, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Achelis, Johann Daniel, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 256)
      See also: box 28, folder 936
    - Ackerknecht, Erwin (father of Erwin Henry), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Ackerknecht, Erwin Henry(*), 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 257-258)
    - Ackerknecht, Erwin Henry(*), 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 259)
      See also: box 27, folder 924
    - Ackerknecht, Erwin Henry(*), 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 260-261)
    - Ackerknecht, Erwin Henry, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Ackerknecht, Erwin Henry(*), 1956 February-Jul, 1956 September-1957 (Box 7, Folder 263-266)
    - Adler, Gret S., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Aerzte Gesellschaft des Kantons Bern, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Ahmad, Bashir, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Airoldi, Leone, 1951, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Babini, José, 1952, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Allan, John Cameron, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Allen, Phyllis, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Allen (George) & Unwin, Ltd., 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Alpstäg, Hans, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Alvarez, Walter C., 1952-1955 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - American Joint Distribution Committee(*), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1948, 1953, undated (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - American Public Health Association, 1948-1955, undated (Box 7, Folder 273)
      See also: box 24, folder 843
    - American Review of Soviet Medicine, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - American Review on the Soviet Union, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - American Russian Institute for Cultural Relations with the Soviet Union, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - American-Soviet Medical Society, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - Anderes, E., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - Anker, Jean, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - Antognoni, Phyllis (Mrs. Enrico), 1954, undated (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Antonini, Marco(*), 1947-1955 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Appel, Doris (Mrs. Bernard)(*), 1948-1955, undated (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - Arasa, Francisco(*), 1948-1952 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Arbeitsgemeinshaft für Gesundheits-wesen, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Archila, Ricardo, 1953-1956 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Arian, Enzo, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Armed Forces Medical Library(*), 1947-1956 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Army Medical Library
      See: box 7, folder 281
    - Arnold, Phyllis(*), 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Aron, William, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Artelt, Walter, 1949-1956 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Arthur, Helen Hewitt, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Asher, P., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Association-Suisse-U.R.S.S., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Astruc, Pierre, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Athenaion, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Athlone Press, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Attinger, E., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Aumann, ____, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Ba-Be (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Bi-Bu (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - Babinger, Franz, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Babini, José, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Bacher, Claire(*), 1948-1956, undated (Box 8, Folder 291-294)
    - Baehr, George, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Baer, Gertrude, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Bakardjiew, Wassil N., 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Balzli, Hans, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Banks, Arthur Leslie, 1952, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Barbensi, Guido, 1947-1956 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Barkhuus, Arne, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Barouch, M., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Barrada, Hoda, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Bartels, A. J. H., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Basel, University of, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Bastholm, Eyvind, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Bastholm, Lone (daughter of E.), 1950-1955 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Bates, Gordon, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Batschelet, Hans(*), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Baudisch, Oskar, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Baumgarten,[Helene?], 1952, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Baumgartner, Kathrin, 1952-1955, undated (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Baumgartner, Leona, 1947-1953, undated (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Baumgartner, Rudolf
      See: box 8, folder 303
    - Bayon, Henry P. G., 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Bazala, Vladimir, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Bean, William B., 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Beard (John) Memorial Foundation, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Beccaria, Augusto, 1953, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Beechhurst Press, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Beer, Francois-Joachim(*), 1953-1956 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Behrsing, Eleonore
      See: box 8, folder 308-309
    - Behrsing, Lydia
    - Behrsing, Siegfried(*), 1947-1952 (Box 8, Folder 308-309)
    - Bell, Whitfield J., 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Belloni, Luigi, 1948-1955 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Belt, Elmer, 1950-1956 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Beretta, Mrs. E., 1948-1954 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Berghoff, Emanuel(*), 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 312)
      See also: box 15, folder 563
    - Berlin, Institute für Geschichte der Medizin and der Naturwissen schaft, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Berlin, University of, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Berman, Rose L.(*), 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Bern, University of, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Bernheim, Bertrand M., 1949-1955 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Bett, Walter R.(*), 1947-1956 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Bettelini, A., 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Bhatia, Sohan Lal(*), 1949-1956, undated (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Bhatt, Mahendra J.(*), 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Bhatt, Mahendra J.(*), 1949-1955 (Box 8, Folder 318)
      See also: box 19, folder 697
    - Bhatt, Upendre, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Bidinger, Godehard Joseph, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Bieber, Albert, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Bieling, Richard, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Bilikiewicz, Tadeusz(*), 1947-1956 (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Bircher, Eugen, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Birkhäuser, Hans, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Bishop, William John, 1952, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Blanton, Wyndham, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - Bleuler, Manfred, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - Bloch, Hubert(*), 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    - Bluestone, E. M.(*), 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - Boas, Ernst P., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Boas, George, 1954-1956, undated (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Bober, Theodore, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Boccazzi, Cino, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Bodenhausen, ____, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Bodhamer, Joachim, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Boenheim, Felix(*), 1949-1956 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - Boerlin, Gertrud, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Bonelli, Maria Luisa, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Bonner, Thomas N., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Bosch, Erik, 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Boston, Hope Trebing, (Mrs. Douglas)(*), 1948-1956, undated (Box 9, Folder 332-334)
    - Botsztejn, Anna, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Bottero, Aldo, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Boudreau, Frank G., 1948-1953 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Bouvet, Maurice, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Brachwitz, Richard, 1947, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Brain, Walter Russell, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Braunstein, Albert, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Bringolf, Walter, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Brinkmann, D., 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - British Society for the History of Science, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Brockbank, Edward M., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 340)
    - Brödel, Lisa, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 340)
      See also: box 25, folder 878
    - Brown, Esther Lucile(*), 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 341-342)
    - Brown, Keith MacArthur(*), 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Bruce, Eldridge(*), 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Bruck, Max A.(*), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Brück, Dietrich, 1948-1956 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Brücke, Franz., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Brunet, Pierre, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Brunn, Ruth von (Mrs. Walter, Jr.), 1949-1956 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Brunn, Walter von (Sr.)(*), 1948-1952 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Brunn, Walter von (Jr.)(*), 1948-1954 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Brunner, Th., 1949, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Bruppacker, Hans, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Bubb, Margrit Fehlmann (Mrs. Werner Ph.), 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Bubb, Werner Ph.(*), 1950-1956 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - Buckler, William H., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Buess, G. (Mrs. Heinrich), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Buess, Heinrich(*), 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Buess, Heinrich(*), 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 352)
    - Buess, Heinrich(*), 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 353-354)
    - Bulani, Gino, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Gutiérrez Alfaro, Pedro A., 1949, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Burstein, Sona R., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Buacchi, Vincenzo, 1949, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Butler, Francelia, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Ca (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Ce-Col (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Com-Cu (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Cairncross, John, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Cairns, Huntington, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Carrillo y Alvarez, Florenzio, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Cassell, Lois (Mrs. Robert), 1948-1949, undated (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Cassell, Robert, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Cassirer, Marianne, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Castiglioni, Arturo(*), 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - Castiglioni, Arturo(*), 1949 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - Castiglioni, Arturo(*), 1950-1956, undated (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Castiglioni, Augusto, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Castiglioni, [Marcella?],(Mrs. Arturo), 1953-1955 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Castiglioni, Victor(*), 1953-1955 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Centaurus (*), 1950-1955 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Cetto, Anna Maria, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Chance, Burton(*), 1948-1954 (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Chandler, Simon, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - Chaumartin, Henry, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - Chavez, Ignacio, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - Cherkasky, Martin, 1949, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - Chiang, Yü-t'u, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - China, Minister of the People's Republic in Switzerland, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - China Reconstructs, 1952, 1956, undated (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - China Welfare Institute
      See: box 23, folder 837
    - Chinard., E. (Mrs. Gilbert), undated (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Chinard, Gilbert, 1952, 1955, undated (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Chinese Medical History Society, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Christ-Wackernagel, Salome, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Chu, C. K., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Chugerman, Samuel, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Citadel Press(*), 1947-1948, undated (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - Clark, Charles Upson(*), 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Clark, Charles Upson(*), 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Clark, H. Heath (daughter of Charles H.), 1952 (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Clark, Rebecca Timbres (Mrs. Edgar), 1947-1952 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Clendening, Dorothy, undated (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Cobb, Stanley, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Cocchi, U[mberto?], 1951 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Cohen, I. Bernard, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - CIBA
      See: box 20, folder 728-732
    - Cohn, Alfred E., 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Conrad, Max, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Cornell University Press(*), 1947-1956 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Corner, George W., 1948, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Corsini, Andrea(*), 1947-1953 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Corti, Walter Robert, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Cramer, A., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Crowley, Alan F., 1956, undated (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Cultural and Scientific Conference for World Peace, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Cumpston, John H. L., 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Da-De (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Di-Du (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Daley, Allen, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Dalrymple-Champneys, Weldon(*), 1947-1955 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Dalsace, Jean(*), 1954-1955, undated (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Daubenton, François, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Davis, Michael M., 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Davison, Wilburt C. ("Dave"), 1948-1954 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Denko, Charles, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Denko, Joanne Decker (Mrs. Charles), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Deucher, F., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Deuchler, Walter, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Deutsch, Albert, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Devrient, Wilhelm(*), 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    - Diaz Gonzalez, Joaquin, 1949, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Dieckmann, Hans, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Diepgen, Paul(*), 1948-1956 (Box 10, Folder 396-398)
    - Dijksterhuis, Eduard Jan, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - Dittrick, Howard, 1947-1953, undated (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - Dodds, Charles, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 400)
    - Doe, Janet, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 400)
    - Doebeli, H[ermann?], 1953 (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - Dold, Alban, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - Dolder, E., 1952 (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - Douglas, Thomas Clement, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - Drabkin, Israel Edward(*), 1948-1952, undated (Box 11, Folder 403)
    - Dubler, Cesar E., 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Duchaine, Jacques, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Ea-Ec (Box 11, Folder 405)
    - Ed-Et (Box 11, Folder 406)
    - East and West Association, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - Ebstein, Carola, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - Eddy, Harriet G., 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - Edelman, Isaac E.(*), 1950-1951 Jun, 1951 July-1955 (Box 11, Folder 408-409)
    - Edelstein, Ludwig(*), 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Edelstein, Ludwig(*), 1951-1956 (Box 11, Folder 411)
    - Edelstein, Renate (Mrs. Ludwig)
      See also: box 27, folder 924 See also: box 27, folder 934
    - Eis, Gerhard (Box 11, Folder 412)
    - Elder, Helen Koch, 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 412)
    - Elias, Leona Baumgartner (Mrs. N. M.)
    - Ellenberger, Henri F., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 413)
    - Encyclopedia Americana, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 413)
    - Encyclopedia of Islam, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Ernst, Fritz, 1948, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Esser, Albert, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Etziony, Mordecai, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Eugster, J[osef?], 1948-1953 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Europa Verlag(*), 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Evang, Karl, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Evans, Herbert M., 1951, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Fa-Fo (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Fr-Fu (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Fåhraeus, Robin, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Falk, Leslie A.(*), 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Falk, Leslie A.(*), 1951-1956 (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Fanconi, Guido, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Farmer, Laurence, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Farner, Konrad, 1949, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Faruki, S. M. A., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Fast, Howard, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Fastlicht, Samuel, 1950, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Feise, Ernst, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Fellerer, Margareta, 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Fernandez del Castillo, Francisco(*), 1947-1956 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Fessler, A., 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Field, Mark G., 1956 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Field, Ruth, 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Fields, Albert, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Findlay, George, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Firchow, Otto, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Fisch., Max H., 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 430)
    - Fischer, Hans(*), 1947-1956 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Fischer, Hans(*), 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Von Fischer, Hans(*), 1947-1956 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Fleisch, Alfred(*), 1949-1956 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Fleisch, use (Mrs. Alfred), 1949-1955 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Flexner, Abraham, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Floersheim-Koch, Maria, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Forel, Oscar L.(*), 1952-1955, undated (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Forrest, William P., 1947-1956, undated (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Franceschini, Pietto, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Francis, William W., 1947-1956 (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Frank, Friedrich, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Freedman, Ben, 1948-1955 (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - Freeman, Allen W., 1948-1954 (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - Freeman, Julia B. (Mrs. Allen W.), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - Freeman, Sally, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - Frey, H., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - Frick, Max, 1953, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - Friedenwald, Harry, 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Friedgood, Harry B., 1949, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Fritzsche, E., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Froesch, Ernst, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Fry, John, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - Fürrer-Proud, Millicent(*), 1949, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - Fueter, Eduard(*), 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 443)
    - Fulton, John Farquhar(*), 1947-1948 June (Box 12, Folder 444)
    - Fulton, John Farquhar(*), 1948 July-Dec, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 445-449)
    - Fulton, John Farquhar(*), 1951 January-May (Box 12, Folder 450)
    - Fulton, John Farquhar(*), 1951 June-Dec, 1952-1956 (Box 12, Folder 451-459)
    - Fulton, Lucia (Mrs. John), 1948-1955 (Box 12, Folder 460)
    - Ga-Go (Box 12, Folder 461)
    - Gr-Gu (Box 12, Folder 462)
    - Galdston, Iago(*), 1947-1956 (Box 12, Folder 463-464)
    - Galdston, Richard, undated (Box 12, Folder 465)
    - Galeazzi, M., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 465)
    - Gambacorta, Gorgias, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 466)
    - Gammeltoft, S. A., 1950-1953 (Box 13, Folder 466)
    - Gantt, William Horsley, 1948-1956 (Box 13, Folder 467)
    - Gattiker, Hermann, 1953-1956 (Box 13, Folder 467)
    - Gebhard, Bruno, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 468)
    - Ceiling, Eugene M. K., 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 468)
    - Genty, Geneviève, 1947, 1949, undated (Box 13, Folder 469)
    - Genty, Maurice, 1950-1956 (Box 13, Folder 469)
    - Gerber, Otto Paul, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    - Gerstl, Otto, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    - Gesellschaft für Deutsch-Sowjetische Freundschaft, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 471)
    - Gigon, Alfred, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 472)
    - Gillispie, Charles C., 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 472)
    - Gillman, Joseph(*), 1950-1954 (Box 13, Folder 473)
    - Glass, David V., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 473)
    - Gloor, H. U., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 474)
    - Gnudi, Martha Teach (Mrs. Dante), 1952, undated (Box 13, Folder 474)
    - Godard, Maxima H. Kuczynski, 1947-1953 (Box 13, Folder 475)
    - Goerke, Heinz, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 475)
    - Gold, Howard Carl, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 476)
    - Goldmann, Franz, 1948-1955 (Box 13, Folder 476)
    - Goldmann, Hans, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - Goldschmid, Edgar(*), 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - Goldschmid, Edgar(*), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 478)
    - Goldschmid, Edgar(*), 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 479)
    - Goldschmid, Edgar(*), 1953-1956, undated (Box 13, Folder 480-481)
    - Goldschmid, Günther, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 482)
    - Goldstein, Avram, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 482)
    - Gomoiu, Victor, 1947-1955 (Box 13, Folder 483)
    - Gomoiu, ____ (Mrs. Victor), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 483)
    - Gordon, Hirsch Loeb, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - Gornicki, Boleslaw, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - Gorter, E., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 485)
    - Gotfredsen, Edvard, 1950-1955 (Box 13, Folder 485)
    - Gotfredsen, Gudrun, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 486)
    - Graham, Helen ("Brookie") (Mrs. William H.), 1952-1956 (Box 13, Folder 486)
    - Granados, Humberto, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 487)
    - Grandmann, Heinz, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 487)
    - Granjel, Luis S., 1950-1956 (Box 13, Folder 488)
    - Grant, John B., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 488)
    - Grapow, Hermann, 1953-1956 (Box 13, Folder 489)
    - Green, Robert M., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 490)
    - Gregg, Alan(*), 1948-1955, undated (Box 13, Folder 490)
    - Grmek, Mirko Dražen, 1953-1956 (Box 13, Folder 491)
    - Grossglauser, Elisabeth ("Lis"), 1948-1955, undated (Box 13, Folder 491)
    - Grossman, Edward, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 492)
    - Gruenberg, Ernest M., 1947-1954, undated (Box 13, Folder 492)
    - Grünthal, Ernst, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 493)
    - Gruman, Gerald(*), 1948-1956 (Box 13, Folder 493)
    - Guerlac, Henry(*), 1949-1953, undated (Box 13, Folder 494)
    - Gürtler, Sabina, 1951-1955 (Box 13, Folder 494)
    - Guggenheim (John Simon) Memorial Foundation(*), 1949-1953 (Box 13, Folder 495)
    - Gumpert, Martin, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 495)
    - Gung, Nai-chuan, 1951, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 496)
    - Gutenberg Büchergilde, 1950-1953 (Box 13, Folder 496)
    - Guthrie, Douglas(*), 1950-1953 (Box 13, Folder 497)
    - Izquierdo, José Joaquín, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 498)
    - Guttentag, Otto, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 498)
    - Guttmacher, Dorothy, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 499)
    - Ha (Box 13, Folder 500)
    - He (Box 13, Folder 501)
    - Hi-Hu (Box 13, Folder 502)
    - Haas, Hans, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 503)
    - Häfliger, J. A., 1951 (Box 13, Folder 503)
    - Hafkenschiel, Joseph H., 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 504)
    - Hahnloser, Hans, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 504)
    - Hall, Alfred Rupert, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - Hall, Peter, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - Hance, Bennett, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 506)
    - Handels-Hochschule, St. Gallen, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 506)
    - Hanhart, Ernst, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 507)